Vibha Suneel Navale

Passionate Software Developer with 1+ years of experience in developing scalable applications using a wide range of front-end and back-end skills like ReactJS, CSS, AngularJS, and NodeJS; along with necessary AWS infrastructural, Git and product testing skills.

EXPERIENCE

Cimpress, Bengaluru — *Software Engineer*

AUG 2021 - PRESENT

- Worked on several products (front- and back-end) that help mass manufacturing plants to bin items based on several attributes such as customer details and shipping data.
- To enrich user experience, I developed features that allowed users to easily work with the interface while adding items to a bin in a manufacturing plant.
- Majorly developed a UI that allows users to seamlessly create bins and monitor their usage while performing important actions on bins and items assigned to them.
- Proactively monitored services provided to users while making sure real-time issues are resolved as quickly as possible.

NS Jain Constructions, Mangalore, Karnataka — Android Developer Intern

JUNE 2020 - JULY 2020

I performed a key role in the development process of an android application for NS Jain Constructions. I worked on a construction material shopping app, particularly for sand. The app was made in Android Studio using Firebase. It is available on Google Play Store by the name 'NS SAND MARKET'

EDUCATION

RNS Institute of Technology, Bengaluru — Information Science and Engineering (B.E. - 9.08 CGPA)

2017 - 2021

Vidya Jyothi PU College, Kolar — 12th Grade (Computer Science)

2016 - 2017

R.L. Jalappa Central School, Kolar — 10th Grade

2014 - 2015

(+91) 81055 00204

- ⊠ vibha.navale11@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/vibha
 -navale/
- https://github.com/VibhaSNavale

SKILLS

ReactJS, HTML5, CSS, JS, REST APIs, AWS, Java, Python 3, C, C++, OOP, Data Structures, DBMS, Computer Networks, MySQL, PHP, Android & Web Development

ACHIEVEMENTS

'Best outgoing student' recognition in academics (2021)

Best major project award in AI/ML track in PROP (Project Open-house Panorama). This project was also VTU sponsored for financial assistance (2021).

Secured one of the top 3 positions in a department-level technical debugging contest (2019).

'Best Outgoing Student' award in 10th grade (2015)

Completed an MTA certification (Introduction to Programming using JavaScript) and scored 85/100 (2019)

LANGUAGES

English, Hindi, Kannada, Marathi